Atmospheric Sciences and Research Center; Records ua450
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1961-1992; 3; 5.5 cubic ft.
  - The Effects of Air Pressure and Water Vapor content on the propagation of positive corona streamers, and their implications to lightning initiation- R.F. Griffiths & C.T. Phelps, 1976 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 606)
  - Comments on " The Role of Electrical Forces in Charge Separation by Falling Percipitation in Thunder-Clouds- R.F. Griffiths, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 607)
  - A Model for Lightning Initiation Arising From Positive Corona Streamer Development- R.F. Griffiths & C.T. Phelps, 1976 July 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 608)
  - Corona Charging of Frozen Precipitation - R.F. Griffiths, 1976 August (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 609)
  - An Automatic Light Scattering CCN Counter- G.G. Lala & J.E. Jiusto, 1976 July 26-30 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 610)
  - Sources of Error in the use of the Marshall-Palmer- Drop Size Distribution Equation- R.F. Griffiths, 1974 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 611)
  - Dependence of Positive Corona Streamer Propagation on Air Pressure and Water Vapor Content- C.T. Phelps & R.F. Griffiths, 1976 July (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 612)
  - Comment on "Theory & Computer Model of the Lightning Stepped Leader - R. Klingbeil and D.A. Tidman, 1974 December 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 613)
  - Field - Enhanced Propagation of Corona Streamers- C.T. Phelps, 1971 August 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 614)
  - Positive Streamer- Droplet Interactions and Their Atmospheric Significance- C.T. Phelps, 1972 January 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 615)
  - Positive Streamer- System Intensification and its possible Role in Lightning Initiation- C.T. Phelps, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 616)
  - Comments on Paper by F. Anderson and G. Freier "Discharges from a Large Positively Stressed Electrode"- C.T. Phelps, 1971 May 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 617)
  - Phenomenon- Energized Point Discharge Current Meter- C.T. Phelps, 1969 March 5 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 618)
  - Comments on Paper by J. Latham & V. Myers, 'Loss of Charge & Mass from Raindrops Falling in Intense Electric Fields- C.T. Phelps, 1970 August 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 619)
  - A Self-Energizing Corona Current Meter- R.A. Cudney & C.T. Phelps, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 620)
  - Aitken Model vs Cloud Condensation Nuclei- J.E. Jiusto & T.D. Lee, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 621)
  - Ams Symposium on the Prediction and Measuremenrs of Ice Crystal Concentrations in Clouds- J.E. Jiusto & R.L. Lavoic, 1975 November (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 622)
  - Cloud Physics & Radar Meteorology- W.R. Cotton, J.E. Juisto, and R.C. Srivastava, 1975 July (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 624)
  - Observations of the Realtionship Between Dew & Radition Fog- K.E. Pickering & J.E. Jiusto, 1978 May 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 625)
  - Factors Affecting Ice Nucleus Concentration Measurements with a Static Vapor- Diffusion Chamber- J. Zamurs, G. Lala, and J.E. Jiusto, 1977 April (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 626)
  - Cloud & Percipitation Physics- J.D. Sartor & J.E. Juisto, 1976 December (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 627)
  - Cloud Condesation Nucleus Counters- J.E. Juisto, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 628)
  - Handbook on Aerosols- R. Dennis, 1976 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 629)
  - Progress of NASA Research on Warm Fog Properties & Modification Concepts, 1969 February 6 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 630)
  - Droplet Growth on Cloud Nuclei- J.E. Jiusto, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 631)
  - A Model of a Supercooled Cloud Microphysic- J.E. Juisto & R.K. Schmitt, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 632)
  - The Great Lakes Project- H.K. Weikmann, J.E. Juisto, G. McVehil, B. Pilie, and J. Warburton, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 633)
  - Synoptic vs. Microscale Influences on Great Lakes Snowstorms- D.A. Panic and J.E. Jiusto, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 634)
  - Snowfall Properties of Lake Erie & Ontario Storms- J.E. Jiusto & M.L. Kaplan, Undated (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 636)
  - Filter Measurements of Ice Nuclei Concentrations & Selected Comparison- J.E. Juisto, G.G. Lala, and J. Zamurs, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 638)
  - Mircophysics & Modeling of Mixed- Phase Winter Clouds- J.E. Juisto, 1976 February (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 639)
  - Instrumentation for the Detection of Ice Nuclei- G.G. Lala, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 640)
  - An Estimate of the Air-Water Energy Balance Near East Nine Mile Point, Lake Ontario- U.H Czapski, R. Stewart, and J.T. Scott, 1970 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 641)
  - On Surface Stress & Langmuir Circulations- R. Stewart, 1970 December 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 642)
  - Horizontal Cooling Towers: Greenhouse- R. Stewart, 1970 April 20 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 643)
  - Feasibility of Tracking Free-Roaming Animals in Natural Environment- F.C. Craighead Jr., J.J. Craighead, C.E. Cote, and H.K. Buechner, 1970 November (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 644)
  - Rountine Measurements of Submicroscopic Lead Particles in the Atmosphere & Their Possible Role In Inadvertant Weather Modifications- V.J. Schafer, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 647)
  - Proton Transport During Hydrogen Permeation in Vitreous Silica- P.J. Jorgensen & F.J. Norton, 1969 February (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 648)
  - Mass Spectra of Alpha- and Beta- Pinene- T.W. Norton, 1972 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 649)
  - Summer Reasearch Report- T.W. Norton, 1971 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 650)
  - A Portable, Photo- Recording Aitken Counter- W.Winters, S. Barnard, and A. Hogan, 1977 September (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 651)
  - Condensation Nucleus Concentration Over the Mediterranean Sea- A.W. Hogan, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Publications), Folder 652)
  - Global Atmospheric Sampling Program: Prospects for Establishing a Troposheric Ozone Budget from Commerical Aircraft Data- R.C. Falconer, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 654)
  - An Analysis of the First Two Years of GASP Data- J.D. Holdman, G.D. Nastrom and P.D. Falconer, 1977 November 6-11 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 655)
  - Electric Discharges Inside Tornadoes- D.C. Watkins, J.D. Cobine, B. Vonnegut, 1978 January (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 658)
  - Identification & Characterization of Asbestos from Atmosphere & Water- R.J. Cheng & A.M. Pitaniello, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 659)
  - Asbestos in Ambient Air Near Rockville Crushed Stone, INC.- V.A. Mohnen, 1977 September 8 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 660)
  - Optic & Electron Microscopy Program- R.J. Cheng, K. Dayer, L. Schuster, J.E. Deitlen, A.M. Pitaniello, 1975-1977 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 662)
  - Catalytic Reactivity of Airborne Particulate Material- F.Menotti, J.B. Hudson, R.J. Cheng, and V.A. Mohnen, 1978 March 20-22 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 663)
  - Consdierations Regarding Solar & Lunar Modulation of Geophyscial Parameters, Atmospheric Electricity, and Thunderstorms- R. Markson, 1971 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 664)
  - Snow Cover Surveys, 1971-1972 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 667)
  - Theoretical Estimates of Sulfate Levels in Atmosphere Urban Aerosols- P.B. Middleton, C.S. Kiang, and V.A. Mohnen, 1978 April 13-14 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 668)
  - Heating Degree Day Determination Equations for Any Base Temperature- B.H. Bailey and J.W. Scott, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 670)
  - Sewage Sludge Utilization in Schenectady County- J.A. Kadlecek, 1978 March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 671)
  - General Composition of Precipitation at Whiteface Mountain- J.A. Kadlecek, T. Fiust, and V.A. Mohnen, 1978 May 4-5 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 672)
  - Ice Pellet Melting: Ejection of Microdroplets- R.J. Cheng, 1978 July-August 31-4 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 676)
  - Jolly Tiger Restaurant/ Colonie, New York Energy Conservation, and Heat Reclamation Project, 1978 August 15 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 678)
  - ASRC Annual Report 1977-1978, 1978 September (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 679)
  - Seasonal & Frontal Variation in Antarctic Aerosol Concentration- A.W. Hogan and S. Barnard, 1978 October (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 680)
  - Frontiers- Dry Ice = Antarctica- A.W. Hogan, 1978 Autumn (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 683)
  - When Winter Comes- R.E. Falconer & P.D. Falconer, 1979 January-February (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 684)
  - A Heating Degree Day Study of the New York Univeristy Campuses- H.E. Forcier, 1974 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 685)
  - Cloud Physics Condensation & ICE Nuclei- G. Lala & J.E. Jiusto, 1972; 1975; 1976 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 687)
  - Ignition by Electric Sparks- E. Barreto, 1979 April (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 690)
  - Information on New York State Winds for Windmills Applications- B.H. Bailey, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 691)
  - Active Nitrogen Induced Chemiluminscence at Sodium Sulfate Surface- E.R. Allen, 1978 August 7-9 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 692)
  - The Chemistry of Precipitation Over Albany, New York- D.J. Allen & E.R. Allen, 1979 March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 693)
  - The Photolysis of Sulfur Dioxide at 313 NM & the Effects of Added Foreign Gasses- E.R. Allen & J.E. Bonelli, 1978 January 4-7 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 694)
  - A Study of Selceted Thermal Energy Storage Materials by Differential Thermal Analysis- E.R. Allen & E.G. Malawer, 1978 August 28-31 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 695)
  - Ozone Measurements in Rural Area- V.A. Mohnen & A.W. Hogan, 1977 December 20 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 696)
  - Project Dustorm Report: Ozone Transport in Situ Measurements & Meteorological Analysis of Tropopause Folding- E.F. Danielsen and V.A. Mohnen, 1977 December 20 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 697)
  - Cloud Physics & Boundary Layer Measurements in Radiation Fogs- G. Lala, M.Meyer, and J.E. Jiusto, 1978 July 4 -August 31 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 698)
  - Ice Nucleus Measurements in Titan Exhaust Clouds by the Filter Method- G. Lala, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 699)
  - Daylight Time- Resolved Photographs of Lightning- R.E. Orville, G.G. Lala and V.P. Idone, 1978 July (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 700)
  - The Thundercloud- C.B. Moore & B. Vonnegut, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 701)
  - Lightning Detection From Satellites- R.E. Orville & B. Vonnegut, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 702)
  - Atmospheric Electricity- B. Vonnegut, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 703)
  - The Life & Science of Tor Bergeron, 1978 April (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 704)
  - Seven Problems in bubble & Jet Drop Researchers- D.C. Blanchard & L.D. Syzdek, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 705)
  - Jet Drop Enrichment of Bacteria, Virus, and Dissolved Organic Meterial- D.C. Blandchard, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 706)
  - Control of Jet Drop Dynamics by Organic Material in Seawater- D.C. Blandchard and E.J. Huffman, 1978 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 707)
  - Solar Energy & Heat-Pumps in a Northern Climate- J.J. Healey & R. Stewart, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 708)
  - A Case Study of a Solar Assisted Heat Pump System: 1977- J.J. Healey, 1978 July 12-14 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 709)
  - Comments on Electrisation de Goultes de Solutions Salires Aquenses par Evaporation ou par Condensation de la Vapeur d'eau - E. Barreto & B. Vonnegut, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 710)
  - Global Patterns in Size & Number of Airborne Particles- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 711)
  - The Formation of Ultrafine Ion H2O-H2SO4 Aerosol Particles Through Ion-Induced Nucleation Process in the Stratosphere- L.Y. Chan & V.A. Mohnen, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 712)
  - ASRC Liquid Ion Chromatograph- D. Bird, J. Kadlecek, V.A. Mohnen, and J. Del Santo, 1979 March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 713)
  - Ion Nucleation Theory- L.Y. Chan & V.A. Mohnen, 1980 October (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 714)
  - The Great Flats Aquifer a Unique of Pure Water in Schenectady County- V.J. Schaefer, 1979 March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 715)
  - Thermalization of Small Sparks- E. Barreto & H. Jurenka, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 716)
  - Ion Composition- V.A. Mohnen, 1979 March 31 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 717)
  - Microphysics & Modeling of Mixed- Phase Winter Clouds- J.E. Jiusto, 1977 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 718)
  - Cloud & Percipitation Physics- J.D. Sartor & J.E. Juisto, 1976 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 719)
  - Aerosol Signature- The Winter of 1977- J.E. Jiusto & G.G. Lala, 1977 September 21-27 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 720)
  - On the Global Distribution of Aerosols- A.W. Hogan & V.A. Mohnen, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 722)
  - On the Variation of Aerosol Concentrations within the Mixing Layer- D. Wolfe, R. Falconer, A.W. Hogan, and V.A. Mohnen, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 723)
  - Ozone Measurements at Several Rural & Urban Sites in New York State- P.E. Coffey, R.A. Whitby, W. Stasiuk, L. Husain, and V.A. Mohnen, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 724)
  - Meteorological Transport of Particulate Material to the South Polar Plateau- A.W. Hogan, 1979 June (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 725)
  - Comparison on the Performance of a Solar Assisted Heat Pump & Air Source Heat Pump in a Northern Climate- D.W. Spencer, B. Murphy, J. Healey, R. Stewart, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 727)
  - Properties of Diamond Dust Type Ice Crystals Observed in Summer Season at Amundsen- Scott South Pole Station, Antarctica- K. KiKuchi & A.W. Hogen (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 733)
  - Technical Note- Recalibration of Condensation Nucleus Counters- A.W. Hogan, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 734)
  - Early History of Cloud Seedin- B.S. Havens, J.E. Jiusto, and B. Vonnegut, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 735)
  - Some Characteristics of the Antarctic Aerosol- A.Hogan, A.M. Pitaniello, R. Cheng, S. Barnard, and W. Winters, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 736)
  - Scientific Papers from the Public Meeting on Acid Precipitation- R. Falconer, 1978 May 4-5 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 738)
  - Science, Success, and Serendipity- D.C. Blandchard, 1979 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 741b)
  - Circumpolar Measurements of Ozone, Particles, and Carbon Minoxide from a Commercial Airliner- R. Pratt and P. Falconer, 1979 December 20 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 742)
  - Fog Structure- J.E. Jiusto, 1980 May 13-15 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 745)
  - Comments on Experimental Evidence for Interhemispheric Transport from Airborne Carbon Monoxide Measurements- P.D. Falconer and R.W. Pratt, 1979 July 18 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 748)
  - Kinetics of the Oxidation of Sulfur Dioxide in Aqueous Solution- T.A. Urbas, E.R. Allen, and E.H. McLaren, 1980 April (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 750)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1980 March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 753)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1980 April- June (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 754)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1980 July- September (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 755)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1980 October- December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 756)
  - Aerosol Detection by Condensenation Nucleus Counting Techniques- A.W. Hogan, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 757)
  - Ice Pellet Melting: Ejection of Microdroplets- R.J. Cheng, 1978 July 31- 1978 August 4 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 767)
  - Light Scatteing by Irregularly Shaped Particles-D.W. Schuerman, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 781)
  - The Identification of Asbestos by Electron Microscopy- R.J.Cheng, 1980 June 22-27 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 784)
  - Physical Properties at the South Pole- A.W. Hogan, 1979 November (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 786)
  - Solar Deminstration Project In a Fast Food Environment- J.Bamon & D. McClenahan, 1980 November (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 793)
  - The Impact of Selected Atmospheric Parameters on Solar Radiation- L. Lewis & V.A. Mohnen, 1980 November (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 795)
  - Wet Deposition in the Northeastern United States, 1980 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 796)
  - Energy Audit Service Handbook- D. Girard, Undated (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 797)
  - A Transect of the Southern Circumpoplar Jet Stream- A.W. Hogan, 1981 October (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 809)
  - Comments on "The Mechanism of the Long Spark Formation"- E. Barreto & H. Jurenka, 1981 January (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 811)
  - Comparison of Theoretical Diffuse Shadow Band Corrections with minute by minute data- D.W. Spencer and R.J. Near, 1981 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 812)
  - On the Use of Optical Single Particle Counters to Acquire Spatial Inhomogeneities of Particulate Clouds- Othmar Preining, 1981 June (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 813)
  - Executive Summary- Conference on Multiple Processes- Including Heterogeneous Catalysis- Relevant to Atmospheric Chemistry, 1981 June 29- 1981 July 3 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 815)
  - Informal Internal Report- Record of Some Experiments In Chemical Precipitation- A.W. Hogan, 1981 October (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 816)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1981 January-March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 817)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1981 April- June (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 818)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1981 July- September (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 819)
  - Photo Electric Nucleus Counters for Areosol Climatology- A.W. Hogan, W. Winters, and S. Barnard, 1981 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 823)
  - Comparison of Several Designs for Photovoltaic Solar Collectors Operating in Alabany, New York- R.R. Perez, 1981 December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 824)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1981 October- December (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 826)
  - Aerosol Minima- A.W. Hogan, Stephen C. Barnard, and W. Winters, 1982 May 25-28 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 832)
  - Study of Electron Waves in Electrical Discharge Channels- H. Jurenka & E. Barreto, 1982 May 25-28 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 834)
  - The Transport of Heat, Water Vapor & Particulate Material to the South Pole Plateau- A. Hogan, S. Barnard, J. Samson, and W. Winter, 1982 May 20 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 842B)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1982 April-June (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 844)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1982 January-March (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 846)
  - Aerosols Measurements Over & Near the South Pacific Ocean & Ross Sea- A.W. Hogan, 1984 October (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 848)
  - Investigation of Marble Deterioration of City Hall of Schenectady, New York- R.J. Cheng & R. Castillo, 1982 August 15 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 857)
  - Radiation Fog Field Programs- Recent Studies- J.E. Jiusto & G.G. Lala, 1983 January (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 869)
  - An Anisotropic Model of Diffuse Solar Radiation with Application to an Optimization of Compound Parabolic Concentrations- R. Perez, R. Stewart, and J.T. Scott, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Publications), Folder 870)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1982 July- September (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 874)
  - North East Solar Energy Meteorological Research & Training Site, 1982 October- December (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 875)
  - Cloud Physics Laboratory Collection of reprints VII, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 876)
  - Clear Atmospehre Effects on Isolation Illustrated by Broad-Band Radiometer, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 967)
  - 1983 Winter Cloud Study ASRC Whiteface Mountain Field Station- N.E. Camarota, 1983 November (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 971)
  - Oxidation of SO2 on Surfaces of Certain Carbon Particulates- E. McLaren, A.M. Pitaniello, and V.A. Mohnen, 1983 November (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 972)
  - Cloud Chemistry Studies at the Whiteface Mountain Field Station- P. Galvin, V.A. Mohnen, J.A. Radlecek, J. Wilson, and T. Kelly, 1983 December (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 973)
  - ASRC Annual Report 1982-1983, 1984 March (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 976)
  - EPA/NSF Workshop on Atmosphere Deposition & its Impact on High Elevation Mountain Forest System Volume I- V.A. Mohnen, 1984 April 5-7 (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 981)
  - Fog 82 A Cooperative Field Study of Radiation Fog, Undated (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 984)
  - Some Charateristics of the South Polar Atmosphere- J.A. Samson, 1983 May (Box 6 (3-Publications), Folder 990)
  - A Study of Black Aerosol- N.V. Ahmed, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Publications), Folder 996)
  - Laboratory Measurements of the Thermodiffusiophoretic Efects on Precipitation Scavenging and the "Petri-dish Microdensitometer" Sample Testing Technique- S. Jin, 1986 August (Box 7 (3-Publications), Folder 1112)
  - ASRC Annual Report- 3oth Anniversary, 1992 December (Box 7 (3-Publications), Folder 1578)
- Minimum Energy Building Project, 1975-1979; 0.54 cubic ft. (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)